{
  "1":
{"front": "Dobrý den.", "back": "Hello."},
  "2":
{"front": "Jak se máte?", "back": "How are you?"},
  "3":
{"front": "Děkuji", "back": "Thanks"},
  "4":
{"front": "Prosím ", "back": "Please"},
  "5":
{"front": "Promiňte", "back": "Excuse me."},
  "6":
{"front": "Na shledanou.", "back": "Goodbye."},
  "7":
{"front": "dnes", "back": "today"},
  "8":
{"front": "včera", "back": "yesterday"},
  "9":
{"front": "zítra", "back": "tomorrow"},
  "10":
{"front": "dopoledne", "back": "morning"},
  "11":
{"front": "tento týden", "back": "this week"}, 
  "12":
{"front": "minulý týden", "back": "last week"}, 
  "13":
{"front": "příští týden", "back": "next week"},
  "14":
{"front": "pondělí", "back": "Monday"},
  "15":
{"front": "úterý", "back": "Tuesday"},
  "16":
{"front": "středa", "back": "Wednesday"},
  "17":
{"front": "čtvrtek", "back": "Thursday"},
  "18":
{"front": "pátek", "back": "Friday"},
  "19":
{"front": "sobota", "back": "Saturday"},
  "20":
{"front": "snídaně ", "back": "breakfast"},
  "21":
{"front": "oběd", "back": "lunch"},
  "22":
{"front": "večeře", "back": "dinner"},
  "23":
{"front": "chelba", "back": "bread"},
  "24":
{"front": "voda", "back": "water"},
  "25":
{"front": "pivo", "back": "beer"}
}